SAMUEL ROJAS

WEB DEVELOPER

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3 y JavaScript
- ES6, ES7, ES8, ES9
- PHP
- React Native, React



- Angular 10/11/12
- MySql, PostgreSql
- Firebase, Realm
- Git, Bitbucket, Gitlab



Autodidact

Focused on the required objectives Scrum methodology

Team work

Kanban methodology

LANGUAGES

SPANISH

ENGLISH

Intermediate-Advanced B2

PERSONAL PROJECTS

PORTFFOLIO

TRAUMAPP

Aug 2020 - Jun 2021

TRAUMAPP LANDING

CONTACT

+58 424 203 21 43

https://linkedin.com/in/samueldear/

contact@samueldear.com

Twitter: @samueldear15 Github: samuelDear

Website: https://samueldear.com

ABOUT ME

I am a self taught web and mobile developer. I have work on projects using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and PHP. Also, with frameworks like React Native, Angular and React. With knowledge of management tools such as Trello, Jira and Confluence, I like to work as a team and help my colleagues when they need it. Web development enthusiast. I enjoy using web and mobile technologies to improve the user experience.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - ANGULAR - REACT - TS

3Dlink | Jan 2021 - Sep 2021

- Creation of screens (Mobile First) and functional components
- Implement REST web services
- Breakdown of activities from screen layouts
- Implement and analyze of Google Analytics

FULLSTACK PROGRAMMER HTML5-CSS3-JS-PHP

Totalsoftware | Oct 2019 - Present

- Develop services in PHP for data storage and consumption of these in views.
- Generation of reports in Excel and sending Mail with PHP.
- Creation of screens and implement services for data visualization.

TRAINE DEVELOPER (VOLUNTEERING) ANGULAR 8 - JAVA SPRING

Fundación Jacinto Convit | Oct 2019 - Jun 2020

- Taking requirements for the development of an internal system. Wireframe creation and initial operation
- Development of services with Java Spring.
- Implement ISO 9001 and I18n regulations for multi-language.

EDUCATION

T.S.U IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

2018-2019 Instituto Universitario de Gerencia y Tecnología

PROJECTS

INTDANET

Fundación Jacinto Convit | Oct 2019 - Jul 2020

OLIMPIADA RECREATIVA DE MATEMÁTICA

Totalsoftware | Oct 2019 - Nov 2020

AFX EXCHANGE

Totalsoftware | May 2020 - Present

EVENTOS QUIPUS

3Dlink | Jan 2021 - Ago 2021

COURSES

- Programa de Ingles como Lengua Extranjera CVA (2018)
- Responsive Web Design FreeCodeCamp (2020)
- API REST Platzi (2020)
- Fundamentos de Ingeniería de Software Platzi (2020)
- Pensamiento Lógico Platzi (2020)
- Programación Orientada a Objetos: POO Platzi (2020)
- Curso de React Platzi (2021)